const comicsQuestions = [
  {
    question : "Which Flash created the Speed Force",
    correctAnswer : 1,
    choices : ["Wally West",
               "Barry Allen",
               "Jay Garrick",
               "Bart Allen"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "Who is Spider-Man's biggest Critic?",
    correctAnswer : 2,
    choices : ["Tony Stark",
               "Norman Osborn",
               "J Jonah Jameson", 
               "Aunt May"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "What Robin was killed by the Joker? ",
    correctAnswer : 2,
    choices : ["Tim Drake", 
               "Dick Grayson", 
               "Jason Todd",
               "Damian Wayne"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "Whaat is the name of the metal in Wolverine's skeleton",
    correctAnswer : 3,
    choices : ["Antarctic vibranium",
               "Vibranium",
               "Carbonadium",
               "Adamantium"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "What is Wonder Woman's 'earth name'?",
    correctAnswer : 0,
    choices : ["Diana Prince", 
               "Jessica Prince", 
               "Nicole Prince", 
               "Dana Prince"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "Deadpool was created as a parody of which DC character ",
    correctAnswer : 1,
    choices : ["Bloodshot",
               "Deathstroke",
               "Batman",
               "Deadshot"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "Which superhero gained the powers of ancient gods by a Wizard? ",
    correctAnswer : 2,
    choices : ["Superman", 
               "Plastic Man", 
               "Shazam", 
               "Martian Manhunter" ]
  } ,

  {
    question : "Which group betrayed Hulk sending him into space?",
    correctAnswer : 0,
    choices : ["The lllumintai",
               "Fantastic Four",
               "The Denfenders",
               "The Avengers"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "What is the name of the terrifying version of the Joker and Batman in the dark multiverse of Earth-22? ",
    correctAnswer : 1,
    choices : ["The Killer Bat",
               "The Batman Who Laughs",
               "The Jokerman",
               "Serious Clown"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "What is the name of the vibranium-enchaned plant that gives the Black Panther his powers??",
    correctAnswer : 3,
    choices : ["The Tainted Lily",
               "The Panthers Rose",
               "The Panther's Poppy",
               "Heart-Shaped Herb"]
  } ,
] 

export {
  comicsQuestions
}